Guide to the Sir George Cranfield Berkeley Papers, 1808-1813 MS 011
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Sir George Cranfield Berkeley papers
1808-1813
1809-1811
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Berkeley, George Cranfield, 1685-1753
MS 011
3.5 Linear Feet
The Berkeley collection consists of letters and British naval orders spanning the years 1808 to 1813. All of the letters in this collection concern the naval operations under Sir George Cranfield Berkeley 's command. They include naval appointments, administrative orders, dismissals, discharges, conscription of U.S. seamen, and coordination of supply ships with the British Army. The letters in the collection were written primarily by men associated with the British Admiralty, the British Embassy in Portugal, or the British Army in Portugal.
Biographical Note
George Cranfield Berkeley (1753-1818) served in the British Navy from 1766 to 1812. In 1799 he was appointed Rear-Admiral and in 1805 he became a Vice-Admiral. In December 1808 he was appointed to the chief command on the coast of Portugal and in the Tagus, which he held until May 1812. On July 31, he was promoted to the rank of Admiral, and in acknowledgement of his services to Portugal was named Lord High Admiral of that kingdom. While on this assignment Berkeley's main duty was to command the supply ships and naval support of the Duke of Wellington in his Peninsular campaign against Napoleon Bonaparte. In May 1812 Berkeley returned to England and retired from public life.
Scope and Contents
The Berkeley collection consists of seven manuscript boxes of letters and naval orders spanning the years 1808 to 1813. All of the letters in this collection concern the naval operations under Berkeley's command. They include naval appointments, administrative orders, dismissals, discharges, conscription of U.S. seamen, and coordination of supply ships with the British Army.
The letters in the collection were written primarily by men associated with the British Admiralty, the British Embassy in Portugal, or the British Army in Portugal. These men include Sir John Barrow (1746-1848), Second Secretary of the Admiralty from 1807 to 1845; Henry Phipps, 1st Earl of Mulgrave (1755-1831), First Lord of the Admiralty from 1807 to 1810; John Charles Villiers, 3rd Earl of Clarendon (1757-1838), envoy to the court of Portugal from 1808 to 1810; Arthur Wellesley, Duke of Wellington (1769-1852), eventual conqueror of Napoleon; and William Wellesley-Pole, 3rd Earl of Mornington (1763-1845), Secretary of the Admiralty from 1807 to 1809.
Most of the letters are written to Berkeley; however, a few are initialed G.C.B. and some appear to be in Berkeley's hand. The letters are arranged alphabetically according to the author; within each author section the letters are arranged chronologically. Copies, as well as originals, are arranged in this manner.
Access Restrictions
This material is open for research.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Acquisition Information
Purchased from Myers and Co. in 1953 by The Friends of Fondren (Whittington gift).
Related Material
For additional information on the collection please consult "A Guide to the George Cranfield Berkeley Collection" by Laura Little, 1976 (call #: WRC REF Z6616.B495 W54) and The Flyleaf v. 9, no. 3 (April '59).
Arrangement
This material has been arranged in the following series:
Missing Title
Series I: Letters from Sir John Barrow, 1808-1813 (Boxes 1-2)
Series II: Letters to John Wilson Croker, and Berkeley Order Book, 1807-1811 (Box 3, 3 items)
Series III: Letters from Casamajor and Earl of Clarendon, 1809-1811 (Box 3)
Series IV: Letters from John W. Croker, 1809-1813 (Box 4)
Series V: Letters from the Admiralty, H. Green, Earl of Mornington, Earl of Mulgrave and others, 1808-1811 (Box 5)
Series VI: Letters From Baron Stuart de Rothesey and others, 1811 (Box 6)
Series VII: Transport tonnage stmt. and letter from Lord Castlereagh, 1809 (Box 6, 2 items)
Series VIII: Letters from Wellington, 1809-1811 (Box 7)
Series IX: Letters to Wellington, 1809-1811 (Box 7)
Series X: Troop lists and report, 1809-1811 (4 items, Box 7)
Index Terms
Subjects
Napoleonic Wars (1800-1815); Peninsular War (1807-1814); Military
Document Types
letters (correspondence)
Places
Great Britain
Subjects (Persons)
Wellesley-Pole, William, Earl of Mornington; Wellington, Arthur Wellesley, Duke of, 1769-1852; Mulgrave, Henry Phipps, Earl of, 1755-1831; Clarendon, John Charles Villie, Earl of, 1757-1838; Barrow, John, Sir, 1764-1848
- Series I: Letters from Sir John Barrow, 1808-1813, 251430
  - Sir John Barrow to George C. Berkeley, 1808 November 11; 251848 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1808 December 1; 251847 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1808 December 6; 251846 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1808 December 15; 251845 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1808 December 16; 251844 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1808 December 17; 251843 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1808 December 17; 251842 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1808 December 22; 251841 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1808 December 23; 251840 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1808 December 24; 251839 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 January 10; 251838 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 January 10; 251837 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 January 12; 251836 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 January 23; 251835 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 January 25; 251834 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 February 1; 251833 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 February 2; 251832 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 February 3; 251831 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 February 3; 251830 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 February 11; 251829 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 February 11; 251828 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 February 16; 251827 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 February 24; 251826 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 February 25; 251825 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to George C. Berkeley, 1809 February 27; 251824 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 February 28; 251823 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 March 8; 251822 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 March 8; 251821 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 March 13; 251820; Copy (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 March 13; 251819 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 March 21; 251818 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 March 23; 251817 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 March 25; 251816 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 March 27; 251815 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 March 27; 251814 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 March 27; 251813 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 March 29; 251812 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 April 4; 251811 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 April 11; 251810 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 April 13; 251809 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 April 14; 251808 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 April 14; 251807 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 April 14; 251806 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 April 25; 251805 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 April 26; 251804 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 April 27; 251803; Copy (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 May 1; 251802 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 May 11; 251801 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 May 13; 251800 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to George C. Berkeley, 1809 May 13; 251799 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 May 13; 251798 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 May 19; 251797 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 May 29; 251796 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 May 29; 251795 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 May 31; 251794 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 June 2; 251793 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 June 5; 251792 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 June 5; 251791 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 June 12; 251790 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 June 15; 251789 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 June 16; 251788 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 June 19; 251787 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 June 28; 251786 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 July 1; 251785 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 July 5; 251784 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 July 6; 251783 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 July 6; 251782 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 July 8; 251781 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 July 11; 251780 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 July 18; 251779 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 July 20; 251778 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 July 26; 251777 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 July 26; 251776 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 July 31; 251775 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to George C. Berkeley, 1809 July 31; 251774 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 August 1; 251773 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 August 5; 251772 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 August 8; 251771 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 August 9; 251770 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 August 11; 251769 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 August 14; 251768 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 august 14; 251767 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 August 16; 251766 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 August 24; 251765 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 September 4; 251764 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 September 9; 251763 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 September 11; 251762 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 September 20; 251761 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 September 21; 251760 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 September 22; 251759 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 September 23; 251758 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 September 25; 251757 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 October 9; 251756 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 October 10; 251755 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 October 10; 251754; Copy (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.c.B., 1809 October 12; 251753 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 October 13; 251752 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 October 18; 251751 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 october 19; 251750 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to George C. Berkeley, 1809 October 19; 251749 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 October 21; 251748 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 October 26; 251747 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 October 27; 251746 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 October 28; 251745 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 October 30; 251744; Copy (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 November 3; 251743 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 November 4; 251742 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 November 8; 251741 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 November 13; 251740 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 November 27; 251739 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 November 28; 251738 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 December 1; 251737 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 December 2; 251736 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 December 4; 251735 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 December 5; 251734 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 December 8; 251733 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 December 12; 251732 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 December 14; 251731 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 December 14; 251730 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1809 December 16; 251729 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 January 8; 251728 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 January 9; 251727; Copy (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 January 11; 251726; Copy (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 January 13; 251725 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to George C. Berkeley, 1810 January 15; 251724 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 January 17; 251723 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 February 3; 251722 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 February 7; 251721 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 February 9; 251720 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 February 15; 251719 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 February 26; 251718 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 February 27; 251717 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 February 27; 251716 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 February 28; 251715 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 March 8; 251714 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 March 8; 251713 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 March 20; 251712 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 March 26; 251711 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 March 27; 251710 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 March 27; 251709; Copy (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 March 30; 251708 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 March 30; 251707 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 March 30; 251706 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 April 3; 251705 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 April 6; 251704 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 April 6; 251703 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 April 6; 251702 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 April 6; 251701 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 April 17; 251700 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to George C. Berkeley, 1810 April 18; 251699 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 April 19; 251698 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 April 20; 251697 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 April 27; 251696 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 April 28; 251695 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 May 7; 251694; Copy (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 May 8; 251693 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 May 11; 251692 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 May 11; 251691 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 May 14; 251690 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 May 14; 251689 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 May 17; 251688 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 May 22; 251687 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 May 23; 251686 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 May 23; 251685 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 May 23; 251684 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 May 24; 251683 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 June 11; 251682 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 June 11; 251681 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 June 12; 251680 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 June 12; 251679 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 June 14; 251678 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 June 15; 251677 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 June 16; 251676 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 June 16; 251675 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to George C. Berkeley, 1810 June 18; 251674 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 June 20; 251673 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 June 20; 251672 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 June 25; 251671 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 August 10; 251670 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 August 11; 251669 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 August 13; 251668 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 August 22; 251667 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 August 22; 251666 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 August 22; 251665 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 August 23; 251664 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 August 23; 251663 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 August 27; 251662 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 August 28; 251661 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 August 28; 251660 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 August 29; 251659 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 September 4; 251658 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 September 4; 251657 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 September 4; 251656 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 September 4; 251655 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 September 6; 251654 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 September 6; 251653 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 September 7; 251652 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 September 10; 251651 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 September 10; 251650 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to George C. Berkeley, 1810 September 12; 251649 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 September 12; 251648 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 September 17; 251647 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 September 18; 251646 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 September 21; 251645 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 September 28; 251644 (Box 1)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 October 2; 251643 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 October 2; 251642 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 October 3; 251641 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 October 4; 251640 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 October 4; 251639 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 October 4; 251638 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 October 5; 251637 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 October 10; 251636 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 October 10; 251635 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 October 12; 251634 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 October 15; 251633 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 October 20; 251632 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 October 27; 251631 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 November 5; 251630 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 November 8; 251629 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 November 9; 251628 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 November 13; 251627 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 November 13; 251626 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to George C. Berkeley, 1810 November 16; 251625 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 November 16; 251624 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 November 16; 251623 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 November 17; 251622 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 November 19; 251621 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 November 21; 251620 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 November 22; 251619 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 November 24; 251618 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 November 24; 251617 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 November 24; 251616; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 November 25; 251615; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 November 27; 251614 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 December 3; 251613 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 December 3; 251612 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 December 3; 251611 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 December 3; 251610 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 December 3; 251609 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 December 3; 251608 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 December 5; 251607 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 December 7; 251606; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 December 11; 251605 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 December 11; 251604 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 December 12; 251603 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 December 17; 251602 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 December 24; 251601 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to George C. Berkeley, 1810 December 24; 251600 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 December 26; 251599 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 December 26; 251598 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 December 26; 251597 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 December 26; 251596 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 December 27; 251595 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 December 28; 251594 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 December 38; 251593 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 December 31; 251592 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 December 31; 251591 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1810 December 31; 251590 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 January 1; 251589 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 January 2; 251588 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 January 4; 251587 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 January 4; 251586 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 January 11; 251585 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 January 12; 251584 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 January 14; 251583; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 January 14; 251582; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 January 14; 251581; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 January 14; 251580 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 January 15; 251579; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 January 16; 251578 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 January 16; 251577 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 January 16; 251576 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to George C. Berkeley, 1811 January 18; 251575 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 January 18; 251574 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 January 20; 251573; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 January 23; 251572 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 January 26; 251571; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 January 29; 251570 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 January 30; 251569 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 January 31; 251568; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 February 1; 251567 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 February 4; 251566 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 February 6; 251565; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 February 9; 251564; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 February 9; 251563; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 February 9; 251562; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 February 9; 251561 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 February 9; 251560 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 February 9; 251559 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 February 9; 251558 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 February 11; 251557; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 February 12; 251556; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 February 12; 251555; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 February 12; 251554 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 February 13; 251553; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 February 14; 251552; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 February 14; 251551; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to George C. Berkeley, 1811 February 14; 251550; Copy (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 February 15; 251549 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 February 20; 251548 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 February 21; 251547 (Box 2)
  - Sir John Barrow to G.C.B., 1811 February 26; 251546 (Box 2)